NGUYỄN VIỆT HÙNG

.NFT DFVFI OPFR



**** 0395746139



hnv2311@gmail.com PHo Chi Minh City





23/11/2001



portfolio.hocduthu.com

PROFILE INFO

Dotnet Developer with 1 year of experience developing web and web API applications using .NET Core, MS SQL, and MySQL. Understanding object-oriented programming principles, software development methodologies, git version control, and agile practices. Self-motivated, proactive, and capable of working independently as well as in a team environment, and also ability to analyze and design databases

EXPERIENCE

Dec 2023 - May 2024

P&B Food Viet Nam I Thu Dau Mot City, Binh Duong Province

Freelancer Fulltime

- Database and Backend: Design database and build backend using .NET 8 and clean architecture principles
- Auth Module: Implement ASP.NET Identity and JWT with authentication and authorization features, including refresh token functionality
- Payment Integration Module: Develop functions for PayOs and Momo payment gateway transactions via API
- Background Job Module: Use Hangfire for scheduled tasks (e.g., daily order summaries, email sending)
- Deployment: Utilize GitHub Actions to trigger and process code builds into Docker images
- Mobile App: Develop a full Flutter mobile application using an existing template

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

FPT Software | District 9, Ho Chi Minh City

- · Analyze existing application code, write unit tests, and debug the application
- · Build and deploy the system to Azure cloud

PROJECT

TsdDelivery WebApp

A system that allows customers and drivers to book and receive orders for goods transportation

All Projects portfolio.hocduthu.com/project

PerfectBreakfast WebApp

Food ordering system and manages stakeholders into a unified process

EDUCATION

2019 - 2024 | FPT University

Software Engineering | Graduated

Degree Classification: Good

SKILLS

Programming languages:

• C#, Java, Dart, JavaScript

Framework:

· .Net. basic Flutter

Database:

• SQL (SQL Server), MySQL

Cloud:

• Basic Azure, AWS, VPS

Others:

- GitHub, Redis, Unit Test (Xunit)
- · Linux OS, Docker
- English

ACTIVITIES

Write and share effective articles on technology and engineering on my blog Hoc Đủ Thứ

CERTIFICATE

Computer Communications

0

Google Project Management **Linux Fundamentals**

0 0

Software Development Lifecycle

0